all right guys this is if you still for
some reason are subscribed to get our
periscope notifications just how many
people 505 give it a little bit up so
when I use in periscope anymore cuz like
it sucks it is dead but we're gonna get
future streams to not lag we're gonna
like do speed tests beforehand and make
sure the Wi-Fi is good and stable Oh get
microphones yeah yeah we get microphones
we'll do it really legit for the July
1st announcement oh we didn't shell for
that and oh by the way guys when I use
in periscope anymore we're moving over
to YouTube live so make sure to check us
out there follow us on YouTube follow us
on on YouTube and you just missed the
stream so they can still be scopes
yeah nobody scobie's that's fine that's
fine they can be Skokie's I mean like
you know I'd only keep YouTube many
perhaps exactly it's terrible no I mean
YouTube's not a brand that has beliefs
that I believe it periscope might be I
don't know anything about them except
the third like that
I've been can barely afford to keep
their servers online so you know I don't
know I mean I don't understand why I'd
like so much maybe it really is just us
but uh no I feel like periscope cuz I've
done twitches and they're much better
twitch is very good yeah anything but
yeah YouTube live so how many people do
we get with that 2500 2500 we don't have
any reach it's also terrible